[{"answer": "Just replace these numbers here with", "docId": "Dead-Poets-Society.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Of course, so what's the problem", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "I don't hear enough rips", "docId": "Dead-Poets-Society.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Mr. my friend", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Mr. my friend", "docId": "Dead-Poets-Society.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "I am", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "You take a big risk by encouraging them to be artists my friend. When they realize they're not Rembrandts, Shakespeares or Mozarts, they'll hate you for it", "docId": "Dead-Poets-Society.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Free thinkers at seventeen", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "But only in their dreams can man be truly free. 'Twas always thus, and always thus will be", "docId": "Dead-Poets-Society.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "No, my friend", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "my friend said that everybody took turns reading and I don't want to do that", "docId": "Dead-Poets-Society.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Gosh, you really have a problem with that, don't you", "docId": "Dead-Poets-Society.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "All right. What if you didn't have to read? What if you just came and listened", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "\"A Midsummer Night's Drea", "docId": "Dead-Poets-Society.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "What is this", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "You gotta get in", "docId": "Dead-Poets-Society.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "No, not just a yawp. A barbaric yawp", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Hi. This is my friend", "docId": "Dead-Poets-Society.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "She's glad I called", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "So, you don't really think she means you're going with her", "docId": "Dead-Poets-Society.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "What is the point", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Well, of course not, my friend. But that's not the point. That's not the point at all", "docId": "Dead-Poets-Society.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "The point, my friend, is, u", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "I don't know, but I've been tol", "docId": "Dead-Poets-Society.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Doing poetry is ol", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "I don't know, but I've been tol", "docId": "Dead-Poets-Society.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Doing poetry is ol", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "What's going on", "docId": "Dead-Poets-Society.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Is today your birthday? Happy birthday", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Yeah, yeah. They gave me the same thing as last year", "docId": "Dead-Poets-Society.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Oh", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "I'm to turn everybody in, apologize to the school and all will be forgiven", "docId": "Dead-Poets-Society.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Damn it, my friend. The name is my friend", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "She's also in that place. Makes it a little difficult", "docId": "Dead-Poets-Society.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Stand what", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Nothing", "docId": "Dead-Poets-Society.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Nothing. But I did it", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "What are you doing here", "docId": "Dead-Poets-Society.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Go ahead, guys. I'll catch up", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Dead-Poets-Society.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "What sound? my friend", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "He's a rat! He's in it up to his eyes, so he rattled to save himself", "docId": "Dead-Poets-Society.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "I'm out anyway", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "Well, borrow somebody else's book", "docId": "Dead-Poets-Society.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "What do you mean, they're all ripped out", "qsentId": 46}]